AKINWUNMI TOLUWALOPE AKINBIYI

20, Rufai street, elewure, sango, ibadan, oyo state. E-mail: toluwalopeakinwunmi1@gmail.com Mobile: +2348142752834, +2349151062107

CAREER VISION or PERSONAL STATEMENT

A nimble, charismatic and a career minded fellow, highly industrious with excellent attendance and punctuality records. A self-oriented; confidence young man with excellent interpersonal skills and ability to work with little supervision. Keen to find a challenging position within an ambitious employer where I will be able to continue to increase my work experience and develop my abilities. A very discipline, responsible and proactive young man, with an excellent vision driven.

PERSONAL DATA

Gender: Male

Date of Birth: February, 2nd

Marital Status: Single
Nationality: Nigerian
State of Origin: Ondo State

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

The, Polytechnic, Ibadan Higher National Diploma

Local Government And Development Studies, JULY 2021.

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING AND CERTIFICATION

Certificate Awarding body Year

Project Management Professional (PMP) - International Institute of Project and - 2023

Safety Management (IIPSM)

Human Resources Management - Chartered Institute of Human

(HRM) Resources Management (CIHRM) - 2023

WORK EXPERIENCE AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Organization: National Youth Service Corps, Ijemo Titun High School, Abeokuta, Ogun State.

Date: March 2022 – February 2023

Position: Teacher

JOB DESCRIPTION

- Prepare, administer and grade tests and assignment to evaluate students' progress.
- Maintain accurate and complete students record as required by law, district policies and administrative regulations.
- Assign and grade classwork and homework.
- Prepare materials and classrooms for class activities
- Observe and evaluate students' performance, behaviour, social development, and physical health.

Organization: Toban Factory, ibadan, Oyo **Date:** July 2013 – December 2013

Position: Production Worker.

JOB DESCRIPTION

- Operate production equipment.
- Follow the company's safety and quality guidelines.
- Maintain the warehouse machines.
- Review on defective products or machinery.

Organization: Fizzo Quality Water, Ajinde road, Ibadan, Oyo state.

Date: February 2017 – September 2017

Position: Production Worker

JOB DESCRIPTION

- Transfer equipment manually.
- Keep the worksite clean to avoid hazards from chemicals and fragile products.
- Review and follow manufacturing manuals to build machinery.
- Check stock levels and report deficiencies in product or raw materials

TECHNICAL AND PROFESSIONAL SKILLS-

Human Resources Managerial skills

Project Managerial skills

Electrical Installation skills

Entrepreneurial Skills (production of disinfectants, soaps, air fresheners etc.)

MEMBERSHIP OF PROFESSIONAL BODIES

- Chartered Institute of Human Resources Management. (CIHRM)
 Certificate Number --- 100047
- International Institute of Project and Safety Management. (IIPSM)
 Membership Number --- IIPSM12876

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCES

Member of Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) CDS Group (NYSC)

CORE VALUES

- Good time management
- Keen attention to details
- Commitment and loyalty
- Result oriented
- Ability to analyse information

HOBBIES

Travelling, Music, Football

REFEREES

AVAILABLE ON REQUEST